♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
- Synced and corrected by AlexandreMT -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Ah, the beach.
So much to do.
Unlimited possibilities.
There is nothing to do at the beach.
Why did we come here?
Peter, just set up our blanket.
I got to put on my swimsuit
that's a one-piece
that turns into shorts.
Once you hit a certain age,
that's the swimsuit you have
for the next 40 years.
Hey, Lois, you remember
that time you and me made it
under the boardwalk?
(MOANING)
When I go back to school,
my greaser friends are gonna say,
"Tell me more, tell me more,"
and I'm gonna say you were a slut.
- (MOANING)
- That was the first time
I noticed you didn't have an ear.
- LOIS: What?
- Never mind.
Maybe we go back
under that boardwalk, hmm?
What, right now?
Yeah, why not?
Let's sneak away from the kids
and go get busy.
Oh, I'd love to, Peter,
but here comes Chris with
a too-much-sun beach tantrum.
(EMOTIONAL): Mom, I tried
to look at a... lady
who was lying with her... straps down
and she saw me and
she said something to her friend
and they laughed!
What lady? Where?
Oh. Stand back, son.
Watch how it's done.
(EMOTIONAL):
Those ladies are really mean.
Come on, Brian. I'm gonna make
you a YouTube surfin' dog.
You know, one of those videos
where you can't tell
if he's enjoying it or not.
♪
- (FLATLY): I love it.
- (FLATLY): I hate it.
ANNOUNCER: Previously on Big Brother,
Tanner became Head of Household,
while host Julie Chen
had plastic surgery
to look less Chinese.
Later, Sasha won veto power over Eric
but not before Julie married
CBS Chairman Les Moonves to get her job.
And Les himself was accused
of assaulting more than a dozen women.
With nominations looming
and Les fired
for his predatory behavior,
the Boys Alliance
of Jeremy and Pablo strategized
while Julie stepped down from The Talk
to avoid uncomfortable questions,
but continues to host this show
and spend Les' enormous wealth.
Who will be evicted tonight?
Will Julie's
craven opportunism ever end?
And what does it actually mean
to have an employee "on call" for oral?
This would be better with a snack.
Seems like a safe place to open
a full bag of Cheez Doodles.
Hey. Sup?
Hey.
Okay, I'll give you one,
but don't tell your friends.
Oh, yeah, yeah. No.
- SEAGULLS: Hey.
- (SIGHS)
Okay, Lois, the kids are gone.
Let's sneak under the boardwalk
and have sandy relations.
I don't know, Peter.
Come on. I am so ready.
I snarfed a bunch of oysters
from over there,
where the foam is super yellow.
Can you do it in less than two minutes?
When have I not?
Okay. Quick, before the kids come...
Ah! Here they are.
Locals have renamed me Sandy Crevices,
and they're absolutely right.
Please have all my mail
forwarded accordingly.
And we were so close to sneaking away.
I'm sorry, Peter.
Well, I guess I'll go throw
this candy wrapper
in the beach trash.
See you in 45 minutes.
(WAVES CRASHING)
- (WIND BLOWING)
- Ah, damn it!
So, what should we do now that
we're finally down here?
How 'bout we do something
that ain't been done
under a pier in 50 years:
have heterosexual sex.
(MOANING)
So, a strange man is changing
Stewie on our blanket.
STEWIE: Hey, mind your business, Brian!
(PETER AND LOIS GROAN)
ANNOUNCER: We now
return to Wreck-It Ralph 3:
Ralph Wrecks the Toilet.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(MUNCHING SOUNDS)
(DEATH SOUND)
Hey, Lois, I know we ain't under
the boardwalk no more, but
(QUIETLY): you and me got
unfinished business.
- Wha?
- Come here, you.
(MOANING)
♪
What the hell? Wh-What is that?
It... sounds like a happy family
dishwashing scene?
Aw, crap, it's a happy family
dishwashing scene.
Yay! We make a good team, clearly!
We work to upbeat music.
That means we're compatible.
They even let the dog pitch in!
How likable!
And the baby thinks he's helping!
He was probably
filmed separately, though.
Notice he's just an insert shot.
- Turn that music off.
- (MUSIC STOPS)
And get the kitchen out
of the living room.
Damn it! What do we got to do
to get some time to ourselves?
Amen. Honestly...
BOTH: You guys are more frustrating
than trying to sell men's suits
in Australia.
♪
(CRACKLING)
Wh... Wh-What's happening?
Oh, my God, the iPad!
Thank God.
(AUSTRALIAN ACCENT):
So, what do you think?
Uh, they're a little long in the leg.
Can you make 'em shorts,
cut off the sleeves,
and make the shirt say "Billabong"?
- Uh, sure.
- Thanks, mate.
I really want people
to see my snow-white back hair
against my brown skin.
Wh-What are we doing here?
Yeah, I-I don't know. This is weird.
- Would you like a belt?
- Eh, I'll take two.
- One for each wrist.
- No, this is not good.
I think we somehow sent
ourselves into a cutaway.
So, what's the special occasion?
I'm marrying my catamaran.
I don't understand how we got here.
All I know is that we both set up
this cutaway at the same time,
and now we're inside
this cutaway in Australia.
That'll be 23 Australian dollars,
- not regular dollars.
- See?
So, you and I set up a cutaway
at the same time
and that somehow put us in the cutaway?
Well, this is weirder
than an uptight guy
at an Eagles concert.
(CHEERING)
Who out there wants to...
"Take It Easy"?
Not me. Do you read the papers?
Look around you.
All right. Well, you want to...
- "Take It to the Limit"?
- Not really.
That would be
a little foolhardy, wouldn't it?
Okay. This time,
I set up the cutaway by myself,
and it sent us here.
Weird. It's like
this is a whole CutawayLand.
And it takes a setup from both of us
to get us in or out of CutawayLand
but only one of us
to move within CutawayLand.
Lois, are you saying that it
takes a setup from both of us
to get in or out of CutawayLand
but only one of us
to move within CutawayLand?
Exactly, Peter.
It takes a setup from both of us
to get in or out of CutawayLand
but only one of us
to move within CutawayLand.
I want to be done with this part.
HENLEY: Who likes
"Life in the Fast Lane"?
UPTIGHT GUY: Not anyone
who wants to get there in one piece.
Peter, this may sound crazy,
but this is our chance at the getaway
we didn't have at the beach.
Hey, you're right.
No kids... just you and me.
And we can go anywhere.
Like... like when we
hid in Tom Brady's locker
and watched him shower.
Look at that.
It's just as big as you want it to be
but not so big
that it's gonna distract him.
There's a Trump hat in here.
Don't look at the Trump hat.
Look at his penis.
All right, fine. You ruined this.
This is more frustrating
than Charlton Heston's funeral.
Um, 'scuse me,
is-is this his cold, dead hand?
Uh... yes.
(GRUNTING)
He, uh... he said I could take this.
Oh, oh, I want to do one.
This is better than a spin class
where the instructor
is just two giant Swedish legs.
- ♪
- (SWEDISH ACCENT): Congratulations!
80% of success is just showing up!
The other 20% is super loud,
five-year-old Coldplay songs!
Yeah!
Who's ready to puke at 5:00 a.m.?
(CHEERING)
Ah, this is great!
Peter, where are you?
I'm a spin class bicycle seat.
(GIGGLING)
Oh, no! The one middle-aged,
post-gastric bypass guy!
(MUFFLED): He didn't clean
these shorts from last class!
It was the strangest thing, Joe.
Peter and Lois were right here
talking to us,
and they just disappeared.
All right, just keep giving me details
and I'll be taking notes
and definitely not drawing
cool TIE fighters on this notepad.
Okay, well, it was 5:30
and we'd all just
- gotten back from the beach.
- (ZOOMING SOUNDS)
- We were all having fun washing dishes.
- (LASER SOUNDS)
- Stay on target.
- Then, out of nowhere, Peter and Lois
get all angry with us
and start yelling at us.
There's too many of 'em! It's a trap!
But, wait, look at that perfectly
drawn Millennium Falcon.
"Roar!" said Chewbacca.
Chris, now that Mom and Dad are gone,
we should have a rager.
Oh, I get those mostly in the morning.
You and me both, buddy.
Again, an insert shot.
We really had a hard time
syncing our schedules this week.
Ah, this is wonderful, Peter.
It-It's like a honeymoon in
CutawayLand, away from our kids.
Yep. Next stop, Paris.
Aw, crap, we picked the wrong line.
May I have your name, please?
Robert Loggia.
Can you spell that for me?
Certainly. That's "Robert Loggia."
"R" as in "Robert Loggia."
"O" as in "Oh, my God,
it's Robert Loggia."
"B" as in "By God,
that's Robert Loggia."
Oh, God, there are reruns
in CutawayLand.
I remember this one. It takes a while.
Longer than it took to get
my iPad back from Chris.
What is he watching?
BBC. Let's see
what's going on in England.
Huh, I didn't know there was a BBC 12.
Oh, my God!
Brexit. Stage right.
Actually, I will take this.
(GASPS) This is wonderful, too.
I've always wanted to ride
in a hot-air balloon.
Actually, Lois, it's a fart-air balloon.
(FARTING)
So, what do you think of Santa Fe?
This is terrible.
I'd rather be in the pancake ER.
- What do we got?
- It was a bad flip.
He got folded over on himself,
so he's still wet on the other side.
- Was he the first one of the batch?
- He was.
Damn it! It's always
the first one of the batch.
All right, get him in a room
and give him 20 cc's
of Log Cabin negative.
The butter burned,
so there's a crispy black circle
around the circumference.
Son of a bitch.
Tell the family he's going
to lose his outer crust.
- Excuse me, Doctor?
- What?!
Pancakes aren't people.
We need this wing for Covid.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
I can't believe it.
Principal Shepherd came to our party.
Welcome. Glad to have you, John.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, no, no, no, no.
Is that girl here who wears
the butt cheek bottom shorts?
No, she transferred to
that alternative school.
Oh.
Do you happen to know if they're
having a party tonight?
What? You can't leave yet.
You haven't even tried the cake.
This cake says,
"You can beat chemo, Helen."
It was on a discount.
Helen couldn't beat chemo.
Dancing on a table, yo!
Things about to get cra... Oh!
(DISTORTED): cra... Oh!
♪
Sweet! A cutaway
about an unlocked
hospital medicine closet.
I chose this cutaway 'cause it's fun
and for sure not to feed
my fentanyl addiction.
("YOU HAVE AIDS" PLAYING)
♪ You have AIDS... ♪
Ooh! And next door
is a classic song about AIDS
that I now partly regret.
What a blessed day in CutawayLand.
(SIGHS) Peter, this has been fun,
but I want to go back home.
- What?
- I miss the kids.
I want to go back.
- I want to see our family.
- But, Lois...
- Is this Mr. Devanney's room?
- Mr. Devanney, right.
That's the name of the guy
with the AIDS. Next room over.
Lois, our kids suck
and cutaways are good.
What's the problem here?
(SCOFFS) They may suck,
but they're our children.
- Tom Devanney?
- Tom Devanney, who in fact has AIDS,
- is next door.
- My mistake.
"Judy Garland Showtime Pills"?
What do these do?
♪ Forget your troubles,
come on, get happy ♪
♪ You better chase
all your cares away. ♪
Peter, enough. I know
you want to have fun with drugs,
but what's the point of drugs
if you don't have kids
to share 'em with?
Damn it, Lois.
We're having fun for once,
but all you can talk about is the kids.
Well, I'm sorry, Peter.
I want to go back.
And with any luck,
we'll get home by wine o'clock.
- What was that?
- Hilarious mom wine joke.
- You think so?
- Oh, I don't think. I pinot.
(LAUGHS) Oh, boy, here I go.
Forgive me, Father, for I have zinned.
- Please-please stop.
- Okay, you don't like these jokes,
but let's see what all the moms
eating soup at Panera Bread think.
(CHEERING)
Well, I don't care if you miss the kids.
I am not gonna let you ruin this.
- Tom Brady's locker.
- Peter, we've already...
Tom Brady's locker.
Okay, Peter, that's it.
We're going home,
and we're going home now.
(SIGHS) All right, fine.
Let's say it at the same time.
This is like the time we were
together with our family.
Wh-Where am I?
Mom? Dad?
I haven't been given a morsel
of food since you left,
by the way. Not one (BLEEP) crumb.
I was just driving a car a second ago.
That's a problem, right?
And now to exhibit the only
power I have in this world.
Stop.
Hey, stop.
He's not stopping.
You're supposed to stop for my hand.
You're supposed to stop for my hand!
You're supposed to stop
for my hand!
- What is this?
- It's just a little mix-up.
Peter, let's try it again.
This is like the time we were together
with our family at home.
What... Why didn't it work?
This is better than being at home.
"We make a better team than" at home.
"Worse than" at home?
"The AIDS person is Tom Devanney,
which is the name
of a Family Guy writer" home?
Oh, God, Peter.
I think we're stuck here.
Yeah. I'm also bummed 'cause I'm missing
that Australian guy's marriage
to his catamaran.
Didgeridoo you take this boat
to be your wife?
- I didgeridoo.
- And now,
if there are any spiders
the size of dinner plates
that object to this marriage,
please speak now
or forever hold your peace.
Go get 'em, mate!
I now pronounce you man and boat.
("WEDDING MARCH" PLAYING ON DIDGERIDOO)
(CHEERING)
Wait, so, when you two disappeared,
you were just doing cutaways?
- And now we're all trapped here?
- In our defense,
we only disappeared
'cause we don't like you.
How did we get here? What is this place?
Well, Chris, it's CutawayLand.
Well, what are the rules here?
(SIGHS) Okay. It takes a setup
from both of us.
♪ Highway ♪
♪ Let me slip away on you ♪
♪ Carefree highway ♪
♪ You seen better days. ♪
And that's how it works.
I still don't fully understand.
(SIGHS) Okay.
In order to move within CutawayLand...
♪ An old-time movie ♪
♪ 'Bout a ghost from a wishing well ♪
♪ In a castle dark. ♪
I still don't get it,
but let's just move on.
What are we gonna do, Mom?
Shut up, everyone, shut up!
First things first,
did you clean up the house
before coming to CutawayLand?
'Cause if it's found messy,
it's gonna reflect poorly on me.
Hello? Anyone?
Hmm, quite messy.
That reflects poorly on Mrs. Griffin.
Sorry to intrude.
I just wanted to let myself in
to your private residence.
Huh. Nobody's home.
Nobody's home?
Principal party!
("MANNISH BOY" BY MUDDY WATERS PLAYING)
♪ Now, when I was a young boy ♪
♪ At the age of five ♪
♪ My mother said I was gonna be ♪
♪ The greatest man alive ♪
♪ But now I'm a man ♪
♪ Way past 21. ♪
We got to get out of here.
Come on, let's think.
Huh, look at that.
They've got every other team's
playbook alphabetized.
Don't look at the Patriots'
rampant cheating.
Look at the Trump hat.
There's a phone.
Maybe we can call someone for help.
Joe was looking for you guys
before. Maybe he can help.
I'll give it a try.
This cord is all tangled up.
What do I do,
Patriots owner Robert Kraft?
Just give it a tug.
It'll straighten out.
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
All right, I'm calling Joe.
(LINE RINGS)
JOE (ON RECORDING): ♪ Joe
is on a vacation far away ♪
♪ You called him up to talk it over ♪
(SIGHS) Oh, yeah, this thing.
♪ So many things that you want to say ♪
♪ Leave your message
when the beep is over ♪
♪ I don't wanna miss your call tonight ♪
Super long.
♪ I already missed your call tonight ♪
- (BEEP)
- Joe, pick up.
Pick up, Joe.
Hey, Joe, what's with
these crooks on Wall Street?
Oh, my God, don't even get me
started on those guys.
Joe, shut up. No one cares.
Just tell me,
are you in the real world,
or are you a cutaway?
Uh, no, I'm at home.
- Why, do you need me for a cutaway?
- Okay, good.
Just making sure you're not Cutaway Joe.
Hey, you know, that should be
your answering machine.
Cutaway Joe to "Cotton Eye Joe."
Call me back in three minutes.
- Joe, we don't have...
- Call me back in three minutes.
JOE (ON RECORDING): ♪ I just called you,
where did you go? ♪
♪ Where did you run to, Cutaway Joe? ♪
- Hilarious, right?
- Joe, we're stuck in CutawayLand.
- How do we get out?
- Well,
according to a 16-year-old
autistic fan in Akron, Ohio,
"In order for the Griffins to escape
"from a theoretical CutawayLand,
they must first journey
"back to the original Family Guy cutaway
with Adolf Hitler and kill him."
That's it! We'll kill Hitler
to prevent CutawayLand and nothing else.
But how do we get there?
Our setups aren't working.
Well, this is where it gets
a little complicated.
"In order to return
to the original cutaway,
each family member must..."
♪ Does anyone know
where the love of God goes ♪
♪ When the waves
turn the minutes to hours? ♪
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(GROWLS)
Wow, Joe's instructions were perfect.
Well, who's going to kill Hitler?
Peter, I got to admit, I'm
not comfortable with this plan.
Yeah, I know he was evil,
but do we really have the right
to take the life of another human being?
Human being? It's Hitler.
Wow, the middle-class morality
of Brian Griffin.
Hitler head, yo!
He cried like a bitch when I did it.
Let's get out of here.
We're... we're back.
Meg, you saved us.
Why are all these principals
in our house?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
You don't want all these nuts
roaming the streets.
Gary, another LaCroix over here.
- GARY: Pamplemousse?
- If they have it, yeah.
Peter? Peter, are you okay?
Wh-What? What's happening?
You've been passed out for 22 minutes,
babbling about cutaways and Hitler.
- We were so worried.
- I wasn't that worried.
Maybe you shouldn't have eaten
those raw oysters.
I-I'm fine, I'm fine.
Let's just go home.
All right. Let me take this
sweet, sticky Popsicle paper
to that beach trash can
that has bees on it now.
(BUZZING IN DISTANCE)
- Damn it!
- (BEES BUZZING)
(WIND BLOWING)